Thank you for watching!
Who is this?
Mr. Kojima has told us a lot about you, and now it's time for the ending.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Kojima would like to make some announcements.
Yes, we're AmeFlash, and every Monday at 8:00 p.m. on Youtube, we'll be talking about AmeFlash.
We're AmeFlash and we're going to be talking about AmeFlash every Monday from 8pm on youtube.
Every Monday at 8pm, please come and watch the AmeFlash nest!
And every Friday from 9pm, we post a video on youtube called "Ame-chare".
This is a video in which we challenge ourselves to do various things, and we have a lot of fun doing it, so please come and watch it!
What kind of challenges do you do?
We've just started a new challenge called "Introdon" and we're competing for the green car.
It's kind of like AmeFlash, where you fight over it.
It's like the American Flush, when they fight over it.
And every Thursday at 24:30, we have a radio show on Interface called AmeFlash AmeFranaite!
This is a radio show where you can hear AmeFlash's noisy and energetic voice that you wouldn't believe it's the middle of the night.
Please listen to it and enjoy the sounds of the night!
Is this radio event coming up in September?
Yes, on Saturday, September 16th, we will be doing an open recording at a place called Kiwa in Tennoji.
It's a volume 4 event, so tickets sell out pretty quickly.
We hope you can make it.
There will be one part and two parts, so please come and join us.
And one more announcement.
I will be performing at the Stapler Idol Festival Autumn New Song Recording Festival on October 29th.
We'll be performing at the Stapla Idol Festival on October 29th, which is the autumn festival for recording new songs.
I'm looking forward to hearing new songs from various groups.
I'm looking forward to hearing new songs from various groups this year.
All the groups are going to perform their first or newest songs at the festival.
I don't think Amefurakko has decided what kind of performance they will give yet.
I haven't decided at all, but I'd like to do it with a gusto, in the Amefura style.
Kojima-san, do you want to take pictures of the idols from behind the scenes in the various staple idol gatherings, or do you want to take pictures with this girl?
Do you want to take pictures with this girl?
Is that okay? Go ahead.
Can I just take a peek at Hulaki first?Can I just take a peek at Mr. Hulaki first?
Sure.
Mr. Kojima, you take a picture every year, and I'm sure the staff will tell you that you're looking at the anniversary there.
Oh, you want to take a peek, Aki-chan?
Of course, Mr. Hulaki...
I mean, of course you do.
What should I do?
I've been a fan of Mr. Takagi for a long time now, so I don't get many chances to take pictures with him.
So I'd like to talk to her and take a picture with her.
You seem very shy. Well, I hope all the fans can look forward to seeing the pictures of you and Mr. Takagi and Mr. Suga after this year's STAPLA Festival.
Lastly, I, Yakan-kun, would like to present you with an energizing tea.
This time, I have prepared a hojicha (roasted green tea) called Kohaku-bocha.
Please drink it.
Can I drink it?
Oh, no.
I got lipstick on it.
It's delicious.
Okay, then.
I'd like to end with a few words of adorable closure.
Akira's camera, please.
Here you go.
Yes, thank you all for watching this.
Please come to the AmeFlash show and swamp us!
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching!
This program was brought to you courtesy of Toshikazu, Ogawa, Pyon, Nacchan, and Toshikazu-chan.
Get a good night's sleep today, and let's all do our best for another day tomorrow.